(Raj:)Okay, I think I got it.
Rock, Paper, Scissors, Lizard, Spock.
(Sheldon:)Oh...
(Howard(entering, wearing an eye patch):)Hello, boys.
(Leonard:)Ahoy, matey.
(Howard:)Noticed the eye patch, did you?
(Howard:)It's all part of a technique
I've been studying for picking up women.
(Howard:)You employ a visual display...
(Howard:)...designed to make yourself
distinctive and memorable.
(Sheldon:)Oh, yes, like the male peacock
with brilliant plumage...
(Sheldon:)...or the rutting baboon
with engorged hindquarters.
(Leonard:)Or in this case,
the bar mitzvah boy with pink eye.
(Howard:)Mock me if you will, but it works.
You show up in something distinctive...
(Howard:)...scope out your target
and toss out some negs.
- What are negs?
- A neg is a negative compliment...
(Howard:)...that throws a pretty woman
off her game, like: